♪ Men. ♪
Hello, Walden.
Good to see you.
I would say, "Good to see you,"
but, of course,
when I see you, it's usually
'cause things aren't good.
Well, if things were
always good with people,
I wouldn't have that condo
in Palm Springs.
So...
what's going on?
Well, I left
the woman that I loved
and thought I was gonna marry
for another woman
who I thought I loved more,
and then...
I lost them both.
So tell me about these women.
Well, Kate was my ex,
but the only reason
we broke up in the first place
is 'cause she moved to China.
Um, she's amazing.
(soft laugh)
She's smart and driven
and sexy and beautiful.
Then there's
Vivian, who's a girl
who knocked on my door
'cause she wanted
to drink from my hose.
Okay, let's table
the hose part for now
and focus on the fact that you
broke up with a woman you loved
for a stranger
who knocked on your door.
I know. Romantic, right?
What the hell's wrong with you?
Isn't that what
I'm paying you to tell me?
Well, if I just
tell you the answers,
I don't get to yell at you. And
this has to be fun for me, too.
Let me ask you
something, Walden.
Have you ever
been able to have sex
and not fall in love?
Only with myself.
Well, it seems to me
you base your own value
on who's willing
to have sex with you.
How do you feel
after you sleep with someone?
Grateful.
Happy.
Bashful. Dopey.
Basically all the Dwarfs.
Did it ever occur to you
that these women
might also be grateful?
No.
Well, why not? You're a smart,
successful, good-looking guy.
There are plenty of women who
would love to have sex with you.
Are you flirting with me?
Walden, now you're
attempting to forge
an emotional attachment
with your gay therapist.
Is it working?
A little bit.
You're extremely pretty.
But the point is,
you need to break this pattern.
How am I supposed to do that?
I'm gonna
write you a prescription.
You need to learn
to enjoy sexual relations
without concluding
that every woman...
is the one.
"Bang everything that moves."
Twice a day, if possible.
Mixing with alcohol is fine,
just not while driving.
Look,
if you do this, it's very likely
that the next time
you fall in love, the emotions
that you feel will be authentic
and not just
projecting on someone
because you shared
a physical connection.
But what if the first woman
I have casual sex with
turns out to be the one?
Wow.
When I'm done with you,
I'm gonna be able
to buy a yacht.
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
♪ Two and a Half Men 11x20 ♪
Lotta Delis in Little Armenia
Original Air Date o
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ Men. ♪
So, Mr. Mardirosian,
if-if you don't mind my asking,
uh, how did you hear about
my chiropractic business,
Adjustments...
(whispers): by the Sea?
You came into the deli.
You asked to pay
for your baba ghanoush
with free back adjustment.
Mm. That doesn't
narrow it down.
I made that offer in a lotta
delis in Little Armenia.
Anyway,
why don't you,
uh, hop up on the table
and I'll try to make your back
as tender as your kebobs.
Oh, my.
Guess this explains
the hair in my hummus.
Whoa.
Those are balls.
Uh, Alan, can I talk to you
for a second?
Oh, uh, uh, just,
just make yourself comfortable.
(dreamy music playing)
(soft chimes)
(whispers): By the sea.
What's going on?
Well, I don't know if you've noticed,
but I haven't really been
working very much lately.
You know, now that
you mention it,
I have noticed that you've been
here literally every day
for the past three years.
My point is I-I'm trying to
get my business going again.
Ergo, Adjustments...
(whispers): by the Sea.
That's great.
And I'm really proud of you.
But why's it happening
(whispers): in my living room?
Because you can charge
$50 more an hour if it's
(whispers): by the sea.
And not
(whispers):
above a Quiznos.
Okay, this is my house,
not a place of business.
It's just temporary.
I-I just need to
build up my clientele so
I can rent a new space.
I-I promise, you will
not know I'm here.
I always know you're here.
Oh, you are so sweet.
This is gonna be a good
thing. You'll see.
I'll never see anything
but those balls again.
(sighs)
Of all the places
he doesn't have hair.
♪ Men. ♪
Hey, Berta, can I ask you
a personal question?
Twice. Once in college and once
with a waitress
from Howard Johnson's.
Oh. No, uh...
Do you think it's possible
to have sex with someone
without an emotional attachment?
Of course.
My rule is, "find 'em,
fornicate and forget 'em."
Mine is "love 'em, lose 'em,
live the rest of your life
with Alan."
(laughs)
I think yours is catchier.
Not as catchy as what I got
from that waitress
from Howard Johnson's.
Thank God for penicillin.
(doorbell rings)
She should be on TV.
Hello.
Is this Adjustments by the Sea?
Oh.
Actually, it's pronounced
"Adjustments...
(whispers):
by the Sea."
Oh, okay.
Well I-I have an appointment
with Dr. Harper at 2:00.
Oh. Uh...
Sorry... D-Dr. Harper
isn't here right now.
Um...
You know what,
why don't you come
and have a seat and I'll see
if I can reach him.
Okay. Wow.
Ooh, this is quite a place.
Yes, Dr. Harper has made
a tremendous success
of his life.
He's gone from having nothing
to living in a house
on the beach.
How does he do it?
(rattling, clanging)
(phone ringing)
Adjustments by the Sea.
Please hold.
Your call is important to us.
Please stay on the...
Alan, it's me.
You didn't have to yell,
you could've just
hit zero at any time.
You have a client here.
Where are you?
I'm stuck in traffic.
There was an accident.
Well, how long till you get here?
I don't know.
How long does it take the Jaws
of Life to pry open a Prius?
Just-just keep her busy.
How? I'm not a chiropractor.
According to the state
licensing board, neither am I.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
(beeps)
Ugh. The one time I actually
want him in my house.
I'm sorry, he's
stuck in traffic.
I'm Walden.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Tracy.
I have to say, the view here
is very impressive.
Oh, yeah.
The beach is
beautiful, isn't it?
I wasn't
talking about the beach.
You're not?
Oh.
You're talking about...
Thank you. (giggles)
Um... (clears throat)
So, Walden, are-are you
a chiropractor, too?
Oh, no. You do not
want these hands
touching your body.
I don't have the
proper credentials.
I do, however, have
a note from a doctor.
Is that velour?
You are adorable.
So, how'd you hurt your back?
You know, it might just
be easier if I showed you.
Easy's... always good.
That's true.
Although some things are better
when they're harder.
Oh, yeah, like working out.
Or what you're
talking about.
I see how you
hurt your back.
I hope I didn't hurt yours.
Sorry for the scratch marks.
Yeah.
Listen, um,
I hope you don't take
this the wrong way...
Oh. I think taking it the wrong
way is what fixed my back.
Actually, that was an accident,
but it worked out for everyone.
Anyway, I...
I recognize that
what we just shared
is something
very intimate,
and it would only be
natural for both of us
to be experiencing feelings
of affection for one another,
and perhaps develop a desire
to share a meal or a drink
or a couple of years together,
but is it
possible that
what might be best
is...
for this to remain a
casual encounter?
Sure.
Really?
Yep.
'Cause i-if you want
to get a cup of coffee...
Oh, I got to go pick up my kids
from soccer. Thanks, Walden.
Aw. What a good mom.
Oh, good, Mrs. Butler,
I am so sorry I'm late.
Oh, don't worry about it.
It's fine.
Uh, no, no, no, it's not. Uh,
we still have a half an hour.
Any kinks you need worked out?
Oh, trust me, the next time
I'm feel kinky, I'll be back.
Here you go.
Oh.
But I-I didn't...
Oh, don't worry about
it. I got to run.
Okay, well, c-come again.
Oh, I will.
Sadly, it's not
the first time a woman
has paid me not to touch her.
♪ Men. ♪
Morning.
I had sex yesterday.
Congratulations.
When's the wedding?
Oh. (mock laughs) No.
This was different.
If the kind of sex I had
was a suit,
it would be made of linen,
because it was
so casual.
You? Really?
(chuckles)
I know. You believe it?
We started having sex,
and I caught myself
trying to make love,
and I said, "No,
no, no".
"This is gonna be
meaningless and empty,
"like two wild elk
rutting
on the Siberian tundra."
You know, only male elk rut.
And only lesbians
who didn't have sex last night
point out stupid animal facts.
(doorbell rings)
I got it.
Hello?
Hi. Is this Adjustments by the Sea?
Oh, uh, actually, today it's Adjustments
by the Closed Patio Door,
because a, uh, seagull
pooped on my last client.
Uh... I am Dr.
Alan Harper.
Uh, do you have
an appointment?
Uh, I do.
But I was hoping
I could see
your associate, Walden?
Oh, no, there, uh, there
must be some kind of mistake.
Walden doesn't
actually work with me.
According to my friend Tracy,
he worked with her quite well.
Um, Tracy?
She was here yesterday.
For the... internal massage.
Oh! Oh!
Well... well, I don't...
know what went on
between the two of them,
but this is not that
type of business.
Okay, I get it.
Maybe this will help.
Oh, no, I'm not really comfortable,
uh, letting you stand out in the cold.
Please come in.
Um...
Thank you.
Now, um, if I want
anything special,
should I negotiate
with Walden directly?
Oh. No.
No.
No, no, no, no.
Uh, uh, uh, Walden...
Walden...
considers himself
an artist.
And as far as
he's concerned,
you're just two strangers
meeting in a chiropractic
waiting room.
Uh, any mention of money
would just upset him.
I understand.
Yeah. Oh, and, uh, here's a diagram
of the human body.
If you'd like, you
can mark the areas
that you'd like him to
give special attention to.
Oh. Oh, my.
Uh, "X" marks
the G-spot.
Oh, oh, good, Walden,
uh, you're here.
Um, uh, I need your help.
Um, could you keep my client
company until I get back?
Alan,
I'm not here to babysit
your clients.
I can do it.
No. Uh...
No. No.
This is a man's job.
I-I'll be right back.
Hi. I'm sorry.
Uh, Dr. Harper had to
take care of something
really quick.
Is there anything
I can offer you?
Well, that depends.
Can I offer you anything...
stranger?
Well, I do see a...
couple things I like.
So do I.
(chuckles)
You've got a lovely place here.
I can't wait to see
every inch of it. (laughs)
That might take a while.
Why?
Is it big?
I've been told
that it's quite big.
(Walden chuckles)
Wait, wait, we're not really
talking about the house, are we?
No, no, we're not.
Oh. (laughs)
Yay!
It's big.
Would you like a tour?
I think that is
an excellent idea!
(Walden mumbles)
(laughs)
Oh, um,
by the way, my name's...
Up, bup, bup, bup, bup.
No names.
Today we are just two
wild elk... (exhales)
on the frozen tundra.
Ooh, elk.
I can do that.
(high-pitched):
Eee-ohh!
I don't know what's weirder,
that noise or the fact
that it turned me on. (laughs)
♪ Men. ♪
Hey, sorry about that.
Where's my client?
(exhales)
How do I say this, exactly?
I had sex with your client.
What?!
I know. And it's
not the first one.
My therapist prescribed
that I have meaningless sex
to take care
of my codependency issues.
Oh, my God!
I know. I'm sorry.
Well, look, look,
obviously, you know,
I can't... condone
this kind of behavior.
But, you know, if you...
if you think it's...
helping you, I mean, that's
really the important thing.
It is helping.
I feel so free.
Do you know what
it's like to have sex
with a woman who never
wants to see you again?
Yes.
Yes, I do.
I appreciate you understanding,
but I'm sure that this has taken
a toll on your business.
I... Here.
Here's... $200.
Oh, oh, no, you don't
have to do that, Walden.
No, no. Take it.
No, I'm not taking
your money, Walden.
I insist.
No, no, no.
(chuckles)
Okay, fine.
Thank you.
♪ You know, it's hard
out here for a pimp ♪
♪ When he trying to get
this money for the rent ♪
♪ For the Cadillacs
and gas money spent ♪
♪ 'Cause a whole lot
of ... jumping ship ♪
♪ You know, it's hard
out here for a pimp ♪
♪ When he trying to get
this money for the rent ♪
♪ For the Cadillacs
and gas money spent ♪
♪ 'Cause a whole lot
of ... jumping ship ♪
♪ In my eyes, I done seen some
crazy thangs in the street... ♪
♪
Hey.
Think I have
another one for you.
I don't know, I think I'm over
the whole one-night stand thing.
Come on.
You said you wanted
to get into the casual sex game.
I got you into the game.
Now you're telling me
you're tired?
The game doesn't work like that.
Even if I wanted to,
I'm not sure that I could.
My penis looks like one of those
dried-out 7-Eleven hot dogs.
Look, I'm not gonna
twist your arm or...
break a finger or anything.
Bottom line, I just want you
to be happy, baby.
Okay, what-what is
the matter with you?
Why are you massaging me
and calling me "baby"
and dressed like a gay cheetah?
Don't hate the cheetah.
Hate the game.
Okay, you know what?
I'm gonna go talk
to this woman.
Mostly 'cause I don't want
to talk to you anymore.
Attaboy.
Oh, oh, hang on a second.
Um...
okay, uh...
Okay. Now go have fun.
♪ Men. ♪
Oh... my... God.
That was fantastic.
Your partner was right--
you're the best.
(chuckles): Partner?
What are you talking about?
The weird little guy downstairs.
(chuckling):
Oh, that...
He's not my partner.
Oh. Gotcha.
Anyway, uh, don't
share this with your...
"not partner."
Wink, wink.
What's this?
Oh, just a little tip.
For the big one you gave me.
Y-You don't have
to give me a tip.
Yeah, right. Like I didn't have
to pay the guy downstairs
for the "Walden Package."
You... you paid him?
It was worth every penny.
Alan!
Oh, by the way,
I think you might be the one.
WALDEN (calls):
Alan!
I'm your whore?
Your whore?!
Oh. What? No!
I mean, "whore"
is such an ugly word
for such a pretty man.
How could you!
You knew I was using
desperate, horny housewives
for meaningless sex
to improve myself,
and you had to go and turn it
into something ugly!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. It just
sort of happened by accident.
It was a one-time thing, and
then you turned into the goose
that laid the golden eggs,
and then into the goose
that laid whatever the hell
I told it to.
This is a new low,
even for you.
Oh, big words coming from
someone having sex for money.
Alan...
Yeah?
Run.
(thud, grunt)
ALAN:
Ow! My pimp hand!
♪ Men. ♪
(doorbell rings)
Hello?
Hi. Is this
Adjustments by the Sea?
Yeah. But, uh,
actually, we're closed.
Oh, that's such a shame.
'Cause I was really hoping
to see Walden.
Oh, I'm Walden.
Please come in.
Hey...
um, just to be clear,
the way this works
is that I pay you money
and in return
you have sex with me?
Yes.
(whispers):
By the sea!
All righty, then,
I have heard all I need to hear.
(laughs):
Okay. Are you... ready to start?
Oh, yes.
But first,
you have the right
to remain silent.
And you have the right to make
as much noise as you want.
Anything you say can and will
be held against you.
I'd like to hold those
against me.
Oh.
(laughing):
Oh, kinky. Okay.
You're being arrested.
Yes, I am-- by your
captivating gaze.
Oh, wait, I'm-I'm
really being arrested?
Yeah.
Oh, oh, God, no, no,
we-we can work this out.
I-I have money.
Walden, Walden, help me.
Walden!
Okay, wait,
j-just to be clear,
we're not having sex, right?
When are you gonna tell him
that was my acting coach?
Probably after
the cavity search.
By the sea!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man